<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Botnets on ROP-Lobsters</title>
    <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/tags/botnets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Botnets on ROP-Lobsters</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:30:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.roplobsters.com/tags/botnets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#19: SolarWinds Deep Dive: What Happened? Then and Now</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 21:30:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e19/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E19: HTML5 Audio ^ Join Austin and Nathan as they discuss the historic hack of SolarWinds. How did it happen? Why was it special? Why are we still talking about it?
They&amp;rsquo;ll also discuss some of the recent legal and administrative proceedings around the fallout from the attack.
Listen in!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#15: Citrix Backdoors, Post Quantum Crypto, Anti-bot AI, and Security for Kids</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 00:01:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e15/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E15: HTML5 Audio ^ Austin and Nathan are back at it! This time they discuss a current epidemic of citrix device backdoor installations, and some recent publications detailing hopeful post-quantum cryptographic solutions. They also discuss the ways some are using AI to fight botnets and current efforts to give cyber security license training to students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#13: DDoSia, Nagoya Ransomware, Confidential Computing and Linux Security</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e13/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E13: HTML5 Audio ^ Join Austin and Nathan on this episode of ROP Lobsters! In this episode they start with a discussion on a botnet with possible Russian ties. They then move on to discuss a push for confidential cloud computing and issues at a Japanese port with Ransomware. The episode wraps up with a rousing discussion of the state of Linux security at-large!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
