<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ransomware on ROP-Lobsters</title>
    <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/tags/ransomware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ransomware on ROP-Lobsters</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:02 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.roplobsters.com/tags/ransomware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>#13: DDoSia, Nagoya Ransomware, Confidential Computing and Linux Security</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e13/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:01:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e13/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E13: HTML5 Audio ^ Join Austin and Nathan on this episode of ROP Lobsters! In this episode they start with a discussion on a botnet with possible Russian ties. They then move on to discuss a push for confidential cloud computing and issues at a Japanese port with Ransomware. The episode wraps up with a rousing discussion of the state of Linux security at-large!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#4: Wiperware, the Second Order Affects of Ransomware, the Cyber Poverty Line, Meta&#39;s Bug Bounty, and a Proposal from TikTok to Maintain Business in the U.S.</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:01:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e4/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E4: HTML5 Audio ^ Austin and Nathan discuss the scourge of wiperware malware targeting Ukraine, the devastating ransomware attack against London&amp;rsquo;s Hackney Council, surviving below the cyber poverty line, and Meta&amp;rsquo;s recent bug bounty payout.
Finally, Nathan continues his TikTok obsession with an article describing the company&amp;rsquo;s proposal to maintain business in the U.S. amidst fears for data protection.
Also, we promised in this podcast to provide a link to a course that would be helpful for those new to security.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>#3: Supply-Chain Attacks, the Future of Cryptocurrency and Cyber Crime, Governmental Ransomware Takedowns, and MITRE eCTF</title>
      <link>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:04:02 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.roplobsters.com/episodes/rop-e3/</guid>
      <description>ROP-E3: HTML5 Audio ^ Austin and Nathan discuss the recent supply-chain attack targeting PyTorch, new trends in the use of cryptocurrency for cyber crime, governmental agencies stepping up to decrypt systems affected by ransomware, and embedded CTF competitions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
